<Publish>
  <ModId Value="95823" />
  <DisplayName Value="Station Entrance Visuals" />
  <ShortDescription Value="Automatically have train and subway lines information at your stations after installing this mod." />
  <LongDescription>
# Station Entrance Visuals for Write Everywhere

Automatically have train and subway lines information at your stations after installing this mod. This is an evolution of the Subway Decal Asset Pack but the difference here is that you don't need to place anything manually. Everything is automatic.

This mod is made possible by Write Everywhere. Thanks to Klyte45 for his incredible work.

## How it works
You just need to install this mod and subway and train stations will start having the visuals. This mod requires Write Everywhere, but you don't need to change anything to get this working

## Station names
It will get the building name to write the station name on the entrances. If you change the name, it will automatically update the entrances. If you have stations built with the Subway Freedom Mod, change the subway module name and the upgrade name to "Entrance #".

# Station Lines
You will see a maximum of four lines by station sorted by number. The mod will get the last char of your line. If your line name for example is "Subway Line 7" or "Train Line 7", you will see a background color of the line and the number 7 on top.
If your line is "Line F", the letter F will be displayed. You can also name lines as "Line M2" and the name will be "M2". There is a limit of two characters by line.

If you are on a train station, train lines will be separated on the left and subway lines on the right.

# Entrance names
The name of the entrances works differently depending on the type of station

- For vanilla stations, region packs and DLCs:
- The entrance letter is predefined, and you can't change their name. It is localized as "Entrance A" or "Entrance B" and so on.
- For Subway Freedom:
- Stations built with subway freedom will have the entrance name as the upgrade name. Change the upgrade name to change the entrance name and change the module name to change the station name.

### Thanks for Klyte45 for all the work on Write Everywhere.
  </LongDescription>
  <Thumbnail Value="ParadoxRes/Thumbnail.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="ParadoxRes/Screenshot1.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="ParadoxRes/Screenshot2.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="ParadoxRes/Screenshot3.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="ParadoxRes/Screenshot4.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="ParadoxRes/Screenshot5.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="ParadoxRes/Screenshot6.png" />
  <Tag Value="Code Mod" />
  <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/station-entrance-visuals.1714344/" />
  <ModVersion Value="2.8" />
  <GameVersion Value="1.*" />
  <Dependency Id="92908" />
  <Dependency Id="75426" />
  <ChangeLog>
# v2.8
 - Settings moved to WE settings tab
  </ChangeLog>
  <ExternalLink Type="kofi" Url="https://ko-fi.com/rodrigmatrix" />
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/rodrigmatrix/StationEntranceVisuals" />
</Publish>